A Guide to the Near East Foundation records Accessions 2009.104, 2010.002, 2010.020 FA406
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2009.104: Near East Foundation records, 1915-2003; 1940-1980; AC 2009:104; 180 Cubic Feet 168 boxes, including 150 standard record storage boxes
  - Project Files
    - Lebanon - Youth Clubs for Lebanon, 1969-1975 (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Mr. Zaylskie - End of Tour Report, 1971 (Box 82)
    - Taich Reports - Development Assistance Programs of U.S. non-profit Organizations - Lebanon, 1979 October (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Allen, H.B., 1955 (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Area Operational Procedures Manual - Revised Edition, 1956 (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Area Operational Procedures, 1954-1956 (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Ford Area Operational Procedures, 1954 (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1958 May - June (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1958 March - April (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1958 January - February (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 November - December (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 September - October (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 August (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 July (Box 82)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957June (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 May (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 April (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 March (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 February (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1957 January (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 December (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 November (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 October (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 September (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 August (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 July (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 June (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 May (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 April (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 March (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 January (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1956 February (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 March (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 December (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 November (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 October (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 September (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 August (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 July (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 June (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 May (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 April (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 March (Box 77)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 February (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1955 January (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 December (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 November (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 October (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 September (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 August (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 July (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 June (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 May (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 April (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 March (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 February (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden, 1954 January (Box 83)
    - Lebanon to Jordan - H J Series, 1956 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Afghanistan - H K Series, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Greece - H S Series, 1956 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Iran - H T Series, 1958 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Iran - H T Series, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Cobb, 1955 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon to Afghanistan, 1955 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Iran - HT Series, 1955 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon to Jordan - HT Series, 1958 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Jordan - HJ Series, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Athens, 1955 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Syria - HD Series, 1956 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Syria - HD Series, 1955 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Iran - HT Series, 1956 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Iran, 1954 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Noe, 1952 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Hayden to Spalding, 1953 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Personnel, 1954-1956 (Box 83)
    - Iran - Spalding - Lebanon - Personnel - Locally Engaged, 1957 November (Box 83)
    - Jordan - Hayden - Personnel - Recruitment, General, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Photographs, 1956 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Personnel; Personnel Recruitment; Personnel Travel, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Program & Policy, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Program, 1954 (Box 83)
    - Iran - Spalding, 1957 October (Box 83)
    - Iran Reports - Officers' Monthly Reports (Month of "Aban"), 1958 October - November (Box 83)
    - Cobb Reports - Hayden, 1954 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon Reports - Monthly, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Webster Johnson & Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon - Sanit. Wright Reports, 1955 (Box 83)
      - Oversize Blueprint, 2016:FA406:030 (Folder SF30)
    - Lebanon Reports - 1956 (Box 83)
    - Lebanon Reports, 1954 (Box 83)
    - A Study of Home & Family Life in Rural Iran by Josephine Vogt (2 copeis), 1949-1950 (Box 83)
    - NEF Foreign Director's Annual Report, 1949-1950 (Box 83)
    - Ford - Syria - Special Projects - $76,681.43 (Box 83)
    - Syria - Confirmation Copies - D2914-D2999, 1954 November 20 - 1955 March 19 (Box 83)
    - Contract File #95 - Syrian Government Agreement, 1947 (Box 83)
    - Syria - Confirmation - D3300-D3399, 1957 April 6 (Box 84)
    - Syria Confirmation Copies D3200-D3299, 1956 July 15 (Box 84)
    - Syria Confirmation D3100-D3199, 1955 October 11 - 1956 July 11 (Box 84)
    - Syria Confirmation copies D3000-D3099, 1955 March 19 - 1955 October 7 (Box 84)
    - Numerical - DD2300-D2399, 1957 March 7 (Box 84)
    - Numerical - DD2200-D2299, 1956 April 27 - 1957 March 4 (Box 84)
    - Numerical - Syria DD2100-D2199, 1955-1956 (Box 84)
    - Numerical DD2000-2099, 1954 December 22 (Box 84)
    - NUM - DD1800, 1954 (Box 84)
    - NUM - DD1900, 1954 (Box 84)
    - DD1700, 1953-1954 (Box 84)
    - DD1600, 1953 (Box 84)
    - Syria Program, 1948 (Box 84)
    - Syria Agricultural Credit, Undated (Box 84)
    - Syria - Agricultural Proposals, 1956 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Agricultural Work Plan - A, 1956 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Ford Foundation Papers, 1954 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Government, 1954 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Government, 1957 (Box 84)
    - Syria Program, 1946-1947 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Home Welfare Report, 1949 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Finance, 1949 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Home Welfare, 1949 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Home Welfare, 1948 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Josephine Vogt, 1948 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Gov't, 1948 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Eyer Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 84)
    - Syria - Home Welfare, 1949 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Syrian Technicians. Kheirieh & Fakhrieh Arabelly: Saleh Ashkar: Mr. F. Faraj, H. Gazal, M. Ghaleb, etc.1948-1950 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - American Technicians' Monthly Reports - General Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Burnell W. Brink - Director - Syrian Area, 1957 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - C.O. Eyer - Program Director - Syria, 1953-1955 (Box 84)
    - Syria reports - Dr. Lyle J. Hayden - Syrian Trip Reports, 1957 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Charles J. Hill - Agricultural Expert, 1954-1956 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Johnson, W. Webster - Syrian Trip Report & Notes on a Re-oriented Program of NEF in Syria, 1955 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Syrian Technicians - Eid Dahman - Sanitarian, 1954-1956 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Hanna Nhouri, 1953-1955 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Josephine Vogt - Kufrane Nursery Report, 1955 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Josephine Vogt - "Social Welfare - its evolution & development", 1955 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Josephine Vogt - Home Economist, 1950-1955 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Annual Report, 1955-1956 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Annual Report, 1954-1955 (Box 84)
    - Syria reports - Annual reports, 1953-1954 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports -Special Topic - The Arabic Agricultural Society of Syria, 1953-1955 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Special Topics - Audio Visual Aid Conference, 1954 October (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Special Topics - "NEF's Program in Syria & its possible application to a Syrian Rural Development Program", 1954 (Box 84)
    - Syria Reports - Special Topics - Rural Health & Sanitation Program - 2nd Annual Report, 1954 (Box 85)
    - Syria Reports - Special Topics - Rural Improvement Program - "Proposal to the Syrian Government for an expanded Improvement Program", 1954 (Box 85)
    - Syria Reports - Special Topics - Rural Improvement Program - "A Rural Development Program Proposal for the Mohafazat of Damascus.", Undated (Box 85)
    - Syria Reports - Special Topics - Standard Oil of New Jersey - NEF's first annual report to Standard Oil of N.J., 1953 (Box 85)
    - Syria Reports - Special Topics - "Tapline" & "Aramco" - NEF First Annual Report to..., 1953 (Box 85)
    - Syria Scholarship, 1954-1956 (Box 85)
    - Syria - Shipments, 1955-1957 (Box 85)
    - Syria Shipments, 1954 (Box 85)
    - Syria - Supplementary Feeding - US Surplus Commodities, 1954 (Box 85)
    - Syria Supplies, 1954 (Box 85)
    - Syria - Urban Programs, 1954 (Box 85)
    - Syria - US Embassy - Daily review of Syrian press, 1957 (Box 85)
    - Syria - Vogt, 1954-1956 (Box 85)
    - Potential for Swine Production & Marketing in West Cameroon. By Charles H. Rust, 1966 December (Box 91)
    - Potential for poultry in West Cameroon by Charles H. Rust, 1966 December (Box 91)
    - Livestock Survey of West Africa by Warren C. Putman, 1969 June 18 (Box 91)
    - A Handbook on Resource Conservation Lesotho Agricultural College, 1977 (Box 91)
    - Botswana Agricultural College - Syllabus for Certificate in Community Development Course (Box 91)
    - Tribal Grazing Land Policy - Senior Agricultural Officers' Workshop, 1976 November 15-19 (Box 91)
    - Botswana Agricultural College - Prospectus (Box 91)
    - Botswana Agricultural College Handbook, 1976 (Box 91)
    - Report of Inspection & Review of NEF Work & Services in Africa, 1974 April 24 (Box 91)
    - Completion of Assignment Report by Richard L. Hurelbrink, 1976 August 23 - 1978 August 22 (Box 91)
    - Livestock & Range Research in Botswana, 1978 (Box 91)
    - Mathematical Modeling of Livestock Production Systems: Application of the Texas A&M University Beef Cattle Production Model to Botswana, 1978 (Box 91)
    - A Proposal for the Expansion of the Animal Science Education Facilities of the University of Azarbaijan by Nephi A. Christensen, 1974 June 20 (Box 91)
    - Fifth Annual Report (2 copies), 1974 August (Box 91)
    - C-193 T.O.#6 Cameroon Special Rpt./Veg. & Other Food Crops, 1967 January (Box 91)
    - C-193 T.O.6 Tour End (Carlier & Larson) Cameroon, 1967-1969 (Box 91)
    - C-193 T.O.6 Tour End Report W.Cameroon (R. Williams), 1965-1967 (Box 91)
    - C-193 T.O.6 End of Tour Reports Niger (Carlier), 1969 April - 1970 May (Box 91)
    - C-193 T.O.5 Tour End Malagasy - C.C.Cannon, 1967-1969 (Box 91)
    - C-193 T.O.2 Dahomey Tour End J.W. Taylor, 1966 January - 1968 February (Box 91)
    - End of Tour on Pasture Development in Uganda - Calvin C. Merinar, 1973 June (Box 91)
    - Folder Unlabeled (Box 91)
    - Annual Report - Tom G. Powell - Kenya, 1976 June 20 - 1977 June 19 (Box 94)
    - Dahomey, 1964-1965 (Box 94)
    - End of Tour Report of C. R. Hatfield, Jr., August 1973 - August 1975 (Box 94)
    - Dr. C.R. Hatfield - Publications (Box 94)
    - Final Report - UNDP/SF Livestock Development Project No. 279 (Box 94)
    - A Report on Livestock Marketing - Republic of Botswana (Box 94)
    - A Handbook for Managers of Cooperative Marketing Societies. Botswana, 1975 June 6 (Box 94)
    - Tanzania - Phase II Livestock Development Project Vol. I Sector Review & Project Description, 1971 November (Box 94)
    - Tanzania - Phase II Livestock Development Project Vol. II Sector Production Sub Projects, 1971 November (Box 94)
    - Livestock Industry Annual Report - Arusha Region, 1971 (Box 94)
    - Tanzania - Phase II Livestock Development Project Vol. III Disease Control Sub Project, 1971 November (Box 95)
    - Tanzania - Phase II Livestock Development Project Vol. IV Livestock Marketing & Processing Sub Projects, 1971 November (Box 95)
    - Life in Cameroon by Mrs. Linda Williams, 1966 November 13 (Box 95)
    - North Cameroon Livestock & Agrculture Development, Vol. II: Annexes, 1977 June 17 (Box 95)
    - North Cameroon Livestock & Agrculture Development, Vol. I: Authorization Memorandum, 1977 (Box 95)
    - Living In Botswana by Mrs. Irma Hamilton, 1973 June (Box 95)
    - Planting A Forest in Niger - F.R. Weber - Forestry Advisor, 1966 August 30 (Box 95)
    - Manual of Office Procedures of NEF in Near and Middle East, 1967 September (Box 95)
    - Proposal for Opex Personnel for Africa, 1973 January 12 (Box 95)
    - Proposal to Provide Services of Technical Assistance in Analysis, Identification, Development Design, & Appraisal Activities for Africa, 1975 January 9 (Box 95)
    - Request for Proposal No. 80028 (Box 95)
    - Project Paper - Sudan - Southern Manpower Development, 1978 (Box 95)
    - Project Proposal (5 sections) (Box 95)
    - Tanzania - Arusha Planning & Village Development Project. Vol. I - PP & Appendices, 1978 July (Box 95)
    - Tanzania - Arusha Planning & Village Development Project. Vol.II - Annexes, 1978 July (Box 95)
    - Tanzania - Vol. III - Background Studies of Arumeru, Hanang & Mbulu Districts - Gary L. Thomas, 1978 Septmber (Box 95)
    - Cost Proposal RFP #50042, 1976 March 12 (Box 95)
    - Proposal for Arusha Planning & Village Development, 1979 January 19 (Box 95)
    - RFP No. AFR-50042 - Solicitation (Box 95)
    - Commerce Business Daily, 1976 January 26 (Box 95)
    - A Brief Statement of its Organization Objectives, Financing, Program & Administration (Box 95)
    - Cameroon Proposal (Box 95)
    - Tanzania RFP Budget File (Box 95)
    - RFP-AFR-50021. For Academic & Agriculture Specialists, 1975 January 21 (Box 95)
    - RFP Project Proposal (Box 95)
    - Range Ecologist Planner Proposal - Upper Volta (Box 95)
    - Nutritional Surveillance in Drought Affected Areas of West Africa (Mali, Mauritania, Niger, Upper Volta), 1973 August - September (Box 95)
    - Jordan -Jordan Valley Farmers Association, 1978 (Box 95)
    - Mauritania Integrated Rural Development (Box 95)
    - Pulse Diversification & Improvement Project (Box 95)
    - Agri-Academic RFP-AFR-50021 (Box 95)
    - Request for Proposal No. 682-0211 - Rural Assessment/Manpower Survey (Mauritania), 1978 (Box 95)
    - Masia Contract (Box 95)
    - Cost Proposal RFP #50042, 1976 March 12 (Box 95)
    - Request for Proposal No. AID-RFP-SOD-PDC-50155 - Design & Evaluation Indefinite Quality Contracts, 1978 (Box 96)
    - Unlabeled folder (Box 96)
    - Request Proposal RFP 70385 - Indonesia Area Development Program (Box 96)
    - Jordan - Water Management Technology, 1978 (Box 96)
    - RFP Tanzania (Box 96)
    - Request for Proposal RFP #7-0004 (Box 96)
    - Request for Proposal RFP #1879 (Box 96)
    - Proposal for OPEX Personnel Agriculture & Academic for Africa RFP #50042, 1976 March 12 (Box 96)
    - RFP Material (Box 96)
    - Jordan - Water Management & Farmers' Association (Box 96)
    - RFP #3004 Academic & Agriculture Result Contracts 15 & 1057 (Box 96)
    - Ghana - Section VII - Project Review Paper (Box 96)
    - Mail - Amelioration De La Formation De Agents Agicoles - Project No. 688-0207, 1977 April (Box 96)
    - 1978 Jordan Valley Proposal (Box 96)
    - Jordan - RFP's - Bios. (Box 96)
    - Jordan - RFP's (Box 96)
    - Chad - Purchasing, Shipping, Supplies (Box 96)
    - Chad - Scotty Deffendol (Box 96)
    - Chad - Misc. Correspondence (Box 96)
    - Chad - Reports (Box 96)
    - Africa - Morocco - Quarterly Report T.O. #17, 1968-1971 (Box 96)
    - Africa - Morocco - Monthly Reports - T.O. #17, 1968 (Box 96)
    - Morocco - Orvil Godman (Box 96)
    - Africa - Morocco - Arlan McSwain T.O. #17 (Box 96)
    - Lybia - Agreement - University of Libya (Box 96)
    - Libya - Bach (Box 96)
    - Libya - Grover (Box 96)
    - Libya - Cables (outgoing) (Box 96)
    - Libya - Misc. (Box 96)
    - Libya - Smith (Box 96)
    - Libya - Teaching Staff Requirements (Box 96)
    - Libya - University of Libya - Ben Halim - Dr. Shagrum (etc) (Box 96)
    - Saudi Arabia - Ministry Agriculture & Water (Box 96)
    - Saudi Arabia - Memorandum of Understanding (Box 96)
    - Saudi Arabia - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 96)
    - Saudi Arabia - Arthur Glidden - Terminal Report, 1971-1973 (Box 96)
    - Saudi Arabia - Agricultural Working Group Report, 1974 (Box 96)
    - Saudi Arabia - Reports (Box 96)
    - Saudi Arabia - H.M. Reames (Box 96)
    - Saudi Arabia - Proposed Projects (Box 96)
    - Yeman, 1970 (Box 97)
    - Cairo Arca - Program (Box 97)
    - Cairo Arca - Finance (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Archer - Ahhen (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Budget (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Carnegie, 1935-1939 (Box 97)
    - Foundation - Carnegie - Appeal (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Colonial Office - 1940 (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Carnegie - Correspondece (Box 94)
    - Cyprus - Colonial Office, 1940 (Box 94)
    - Cyprus - A-Z (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Health (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Home Welfare (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Loram, Chas A. (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Special (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Miscellaneous (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Palmer, Sir H. Richmond - Government of Cyprus (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Publicity (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Weston, John, 1936 (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - Weston, 1937 (Box 97)
    - Cyprus - White, Geo. (Box 97)
    - Ethiopia - Leasure, Mr. & Mrs. F.G. (Box 97)
    - Ethiopia - General (Box 97)
    - Copy of Notes on "Exploratory Activities" in Ethiopia, 1944 June - 1945 July (Box 107)
    - Ethiopia - Finance (Box 107)
    - Ethiopia textbooks (Box 107)
    - Iraq (Box 107)
    - Palestine - Scholarship (Box 107)
    - Alpha "A", 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Barclay Acheson (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Dr. H.B. Allen, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Allen's USA Trips, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Allen, Miller, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions (Box 107)
    - Alpha - American Express, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - American Foundation for Overseas Blind, 1949 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - American Friends of Greece, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - American Friends Service Committee, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - "An", 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Allen, Crawther (Box 107)
    - Alpha - B, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Dr. Howard W. Beers, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Sheik Hanna Bisharat (Box 107)
    - Miss Dorothy Blewett, Gulfport, FL, 1948 December 1 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Dorothy Blewett (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Miss Dorothy Blewett, 1947 (Box 107)
    - Brethren Relief Center, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Edwin M. Bulkley, Jr., 1948 (Box 107)
    - Chautauqua Society, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - C, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Cornell University, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Mr. C.I. Crowther, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Crowther, Allen, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Crowther to Becker (Box 107)
    - Crowther to Blewett (Box 107)
    - Crowther to Mrs. Egan - Alpha, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Mr. Crowther to Ewald (Box 107)
    - Crowther to Hermanny - Alpha, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Crowther to Kent - Alpha, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Mr. Crowther to MacDougall (Box 107)
    - Crowther to Miller - Alpha, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Crowther to Wallin - Alpha, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Crowther to Williams, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - D, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - "Do", 1948 (Box 107)
    - Harvey N. Davis - Alpha, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Dietrek, 1948 (Box 107)
    - Alpha - Dr. Bayard Dodge, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Cleveland E. Dodge, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Cleveland H. Dodge Foundation, Inc., 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Dr. W. E. Doughty, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - E, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Dr. F.I. Elliott, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Ewald, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Fo, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - F, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Mrs. John H. Finley, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Dr. Edgar J. Fisher, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Go, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - G, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Dr. Fred F. Goodsell, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Bell Greve, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Gulf Oil Corporation, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Arthur K. Getman, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - H, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Lincoln B. Hale, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Harold Hatch, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Dr. C. Howard Hatcher, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Mrs. Hermanny, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Mr. Harry Hill, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Hurdman and Cranstoun, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - In, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Church Committee on Overseas Relief & Reconstruction (Box 108)
    - Alpha - J, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Dr. Thomas Jesse Jones, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Map of Washington D.C. (Box 108)
    - Council on Foreign Relations - Walter H. Mallory (Box 108)
    - American Near East Society Bulletins, 1949 (Box 108)
    - Near East Service Quarterly, 1931-1935, 1941; 1931-1935 (Box 108)
    - Trans Jordan - Saudi Arabia (Box 108)
    - To follow up with Mr. Crowder - Ewald (Box 108)
    - Archer Letters - Athens (Box 108)
    - Arab Memos (Box 108)
    - American Friends of Greece (Box 108)
    - American Council of Voluntary Agencies for Foreign Service, Inc. (Box 108)
    - Racing the Red Sale - Promotional Correspondence (Box 108)
    - Arabian Pipe Line Clippings (Box 108)
    - Armenia and The Greeks - Book of Hellenic Recipes (Published), 1942 October (Box 108)
    - Armenia (Box 108)
    - Broadcasts - Scripts, Copies (Box 108)
    - CARE - Co-operative for American Remittances Europe (Box 108)
    - Co-operative American Remittances Europe - CARE (Box 108)
    - Central Bureau for Relief of the Evangelical Churches of Europe. Dr. Adolph Keller (Box 108)
    - Child Welfare Com. - Rose Ewald (Box 108)
    - Commission to Study the Organization of peace, 1942, 1943, 1944 (Box 108)
    - Harmon Foundation - Fred S. Wythe - Working on strip film for story (Box 108)
    - Cloth for Children of Greece (Box 108)
    - Alpha - Florence Spencer Duryea, 1948 (Box 108)
    - Trade Agreement - Economic Reports - Financial Reports for Reference - Miscellaneous (Box 108)
    - East & West Association (Box 108)
    - Ethnographic Board, Smithsonian Institution Building, Washington D.C. (Box 108)
    - Forums - Miscellaneous (Box 108)
    - Finch Junior College Training Classes - Miss Beatrice Desfosses - Director Public Relations (Box 108)
    - Bulletin - Battle for Survival - Greek Recovery Program Coordinating Office, 1949 (Box 108)
    - Loose papers unlabeled (Box 108)
    - Greece - Girl Scouts (Box 108)
    - Jews in Greece esp. Salonica Report (Box 108)
    - Athens Shipments Complete. Memorandum for Reference (Box 108)
    - Greek National Hymn in English (Box 108)
    - Greece,Yugoslavia, Relief & recon exerpts etc. for possible use. Misc. (Box 108)
    - Greece Reports & UNRRA Items (Box 108)
    - Greece - Relief Items (Box 108)
    - Greece Items of Conditions (Box 108)
    - Mayston, Dr. Elizabeth Horeftis (Box 109)
    - Greece - Graphs - Burned Villages; Hostels (Box 109)
    - Greece - News Clippings (Box 109)
    - Repatriation - Greeks, Turks, Bulgars (Box 109)
    - Liberation of Greece, 1944 October (Box 109)
    - Greece (Box 109)
    - Graphs - Farm Mechanics Training Livestock Project (Box 109)
    - Greece - Newspaper Articles - Geo. Weller & others. For Reference (Box 96)
    - Greater NY Fund (Box 109)
    - Rebuilding Greece (Box 109)
    - Herbert Hoover's Book reviews. Also clippings, Rebuilding World (Box 109)
    - Precilla Hill, Paris (Box 109)
    - Hunter College (Box 109)
    - Greece - Misc. Information Items. Occupation (Box 109)
    - Greece - Map and Info. (Box 109)